{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete Finishers \u0026 Overlay Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40876/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40876,"taskName":"Concrete Finishing, Overlays \u0026 Coloring - Apply","taskDescription":"Apply concrete finish, overlay, or coloring to existing concrete","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete Finishers \u0026 Overlay Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":300,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"concrete special finishing overlay coloring","textMessagingName":"Spec Fin Concrete","rolloverLongDesc":"Techniques can be used over old \u0026 new concrete. Specialty coatings \u0026 techniques that include overlays, selectively masking \u0026/or dying are used to create an attractive \"pebbly\" or simulated brick or stone look. Can extend the life of old concrete that only has surface wear. Aesthetic effects can be dramatic. Includes application of a basic, non-decorative resurfacing product.","rolloverShortDesc":"Decorative overlays and coloring applied to existing concrete","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply concrete finishes, overlays, or coloring. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated concrete finishing contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Concrete Overlay \u0026 Finishing Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Coloring","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Concrete Finishing, Overlay, or Coloring Apply","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Concrete Overlays, coloring, or special finishes - Apply","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Finishing or Overlay Project","urlName":"Concrete-Finishing-Overlay-or-Coloring","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Finishing \u0026 Overlay Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"concrete,finishing,overlay,coloring","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1436,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40876/":{"taskOID":40876,"originalTaskOID":40876,"setID":1436,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7040,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the special finishes be applied? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10503,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior finished floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior finished floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10504,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10505,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10506,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior walkway","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10507,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10508,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10509,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10510,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10511,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Pool deck","answerDisplayText":"Pool deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7041,"questionDisplayText":"Special Finishes","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of concrete finishes are you interested in? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10512,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brushed (slip resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brushed (slip resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10513,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Salt finished","answerDisplayText":"Salt finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10514,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Overlayment (new layer applied over existing concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Overlayment (new layer applied over existing concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10515,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Design stenciled or etched into concrete","answerDisplayText":"Design stenciled or etched into concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10516,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Granite or Slate simulation","answerDisplayText":"Granite or Slate simulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10517,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick or cobblestone simulation","answerDisplayText":"Brick or cobblestone simulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10518,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Colored exposed aggregate (stones)","answerDisplayText":"Colored exposed aggregate (stones)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10519,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Shiny wet look sealer","answerDisplayText":"Shiny wet look sealer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10520,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Colored concrete","answerDisplayText":"Colored concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10521,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Plain concrete with decorative borders","answerDisplayText":"Plain concrete with decorative borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10522,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Smooth troweled finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth troweled finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10523,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Complement house/yard","answerDisplayText":"Complement house/yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10524,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Match a sample","answerDisplayText":"Match a sample","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7040,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the special finishes be applied? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10503,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior finished floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior finished floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10504,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10505,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10506,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior walkway","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10507,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10508,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10509,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10510,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10511,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Pool deck","answerDisplayText":"Pool deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10503,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior finished floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior finished floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10504,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10505,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10506,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior walkway","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10507,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10508,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10509,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10510,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10511,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Pool deck","answerDisplayText":"Pool deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7041,"questionDisplayText":"Special Finishes","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of concrete finishes are you interested in? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10512,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brushed (slip resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brushed (slip resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10513,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Salt finished","answerDisplayText":"Salt finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10514,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Overlayment (new layer applied over existing concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Overlayment (new layer applied over existing concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10515,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Design stenciled or etched into concrete","answerDisplayText":"Design stenciled or etched into concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10516,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Granite or Slate simulation","answerDisplayText":"Granite or Slate simulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10517,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick or cobblestone simulation","answerDisplayText":"Brick or cobblestone simulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10518,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Colored exposed aggregate (stones)","answerDisplayText":"Colored exposed aggregate (stones)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10519,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Shiny wet look sealer","answerDisplayText":"Shiny wet look sealer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10520,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Colored concrete","answerDisplayText":"Colored concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10521,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Plain concrete with decorative borders","answerDisplayText":"Plain concrete with decorative borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10522,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Smooth troweled finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth troweled finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10523,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Complement house/yard","answerDisplayText":"Complement house/yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10524,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Match a sample","answerDisplayText":"Match a sample","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10512,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brushed (slip resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brushed (slip resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10513,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Salt finished","answerDisplayText":"Salt finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10514,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Overlayment (new layer applied over existing concrete)","answerDisplayText":"Overlayment (new layer applied over existing concrete)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10515,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Design stenciled or etched into concrete","answerDisplayText":"Design stenciled or etched into concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10516,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Granite or Slate simulation","answerDisplayText":"Granite or Slate simulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10517,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick or cobblestone simulation","answerDisplayText":"Brick or cobblestone simulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10518,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Colored exposed aggregate (stones)","answerDisplayText":"Colored exposed aggregate (stones)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10519,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Shiny wet look sealer","answerDisplayText":"Shiny wet look sealer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10520,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Colored concrete","answerDisplayText":"Colored concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10521,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Plain concrete with decorative borders","answerDisplayText":"Plain concrete with decorative borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10522,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Smooth troweled finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth troweled finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10523,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Complement house/yard","answerDisplayText":"Complement house/yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10524,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Match a sample","answerDisplayText":"Match a sample","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}